<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Visit Cluj</string>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <string name="must_do">Must Do</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="nightlife">Nightlife</string>

    <!-- Descriptions -->
    //Must Do category
    <string name="cheile_turzii_description">They are a protected natural reservation in Romania,
        located at a distance of 6 km west from Turda, along the valley Hasdate.
        The length of the of the Turda Keys is of 2.900 m. The walls height is up to 300 m.
        The surface occupied by the Keys is of 125 ha and were formed by the erosion of the jurassic limestone rock by the river Hasdate.</string>
    <string name="cetatuia_description">It is a fortification built during the Habsburg period
        on the top of the hill with the same name in Cluj-Napoca, in the Gruia district</string>
    <string name="salina_turda_description">The Salt Mine is now a veritable history museum of salt mining.
        The excellent state of preservation of mining and machinery used to transport salt,
        together with the cautious work carried out for prepararing the mine to become a tourist attraction,
        have made history and legend meet harmoniously here.</string>
    <string name="michaels_church_description">It is a Gothic-style Roman Catholic church in Cluj-Napoca.
        It is the second largest church (after the Black Church of Brașov) in the geographical region of Transylvania, Romania.</string>
    <string name="king_matthias_description">This classified historic monument, conceived by János Fadrusz and opened in 1902,
        represents Matthias Corvinus. It is a historic monument in Romania</string>


    //Parks category
    <string name="central_park_description">The park is bounded by the Cluj Arena to the west, the Hungarian State Theater to the East,
        the Somesul Mic River to the north, and the Iuliu Hossu (formerly Pavlov) to the south. It is listed on the historical monuments list in Cluj County</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_description">In addition to its role as a tourist destination,
        the garden also serves as a teaching and research center as part of the Babeș-Bolyai University.
        In 2010, the Romanian Ministry of Culture and National Patrimony categorized it as a historical monument.</string>
    <string name="iulius_park_description">It is a small park featuring a lake and it is situated in the vecinity of Iulius Mall.</string>
    <string name="rozelor_park_description">A very old park in one of the older neighbourhoods of the city. It has recently been revamped and
        features a brand new Skatepark.</string>
    <string name="gheorgheni_park_description">The most modern sports and leisure complex in Cluj made with European funds.</string>


    //Shopping category
    <string name="iulius_mall_description">Opened in 2007 and oriented towards multiculturalism,
        IULIUS MALL CLUJ provides an original mix of its multiple uses and the fondness of Transylvanian locals for art in all its forms.</string>
    <string name="vivo_mall_description">VIVO! was launched in October 2014. The brand represents the shopping centers that address small
        and medium-sized towns in the urban agglomerations in the east and central Europe. </string>
    <string name="platinia_description">Features 30 shops of recognized international. A great place to dine. 14 new events organized every month.</string>

    //History category
    <string name="theotokos_cathedral_description">is the most famous Romanian Orthodox church of Cluj-Napoca, Romania.
        Built in a Romanian Brâncovenesc style, a synthesis of Renaissance and Byzantine architecture, it lies on the Avram Iancu Square</string>
    <string name="franciscan_church_description"> is a place of worship in Cluj-Napoca, Romania. It was built between 1260 and 1290,
        on the site of an older Catholic church destroyed during the Tatar invasions in 1241.</string>
    <string name="ethnografic_museum_description">With a history of more than 80 years, the Ethnographic Museum of Transylvania is
        one of the first and greatest of its kind in Romania. It has two exhibition sections, one of which is to be found in downtown Reduta Palace
        (21, Memorandumului Street), while the other exhibition section is the open-air Romulus Vuia Park situated on the city\'s north-west side, in Hoia Forest.</string>
    <string name="pharmacy_museum_description">The Pharmacy History Collection can be found in the oldest pharmacy building of Cluj-Napoca,
        named “La Sfântul Gheorghe”, also known as the Hintz pharmacy, dating back to 1573.</string>
    <string name="art_museum_description">With a collection of over 12,000 paintings, sculptures,
        graphic arts and decorative pieces, it is considered one of the most important museums in Romania.</string>
    <string name="observatory_description">Since 2008 the Observatory organizes activities for the general public also.
        Visitors are welcome every Friday night, after dark, for a program scheduled for 2 hours.
        It consists of an introduction (projecting a simulated configuration of the sky map of the moment accompanied by an explanation
        of the celestial objects that will be observed), and a practical, observational part, using the existing instruments.</string>

    //Nightlife category
    <string name="londoner_pub_description">Londoner takes us to London, where people have a strange but sophisticated accent,
        where we seem to look through the fogs and the specific English hats.</string>
    <string name="flying_circus_pub_description">Located in the historic center of the city, in the basement of a building,
        Flying Circus Pub is a club for young indie, rock, punk, or electronic music lovers.</string>
    <string name="shto_bar_description">Shto College Bar is the place where you can find good music,
        fine people, products for all tastes and a very friendly atmosphere!</string>
    <string name="bruno_wine_bar_description">The Bruno Wine Bar and Bistro, a little spotless, an introduction to the particularities of wines on 4 continents,
        in the careful balance of "l'apéritif et le digestif" plus a selection of fine cheeses and snacks in perfectly balanced combinations
        because at just as with a successful "marriage", wine and food can not be separated. </string>
    <string name="jazz_pub_description">Casa Tauffer is the only exclusive jazz and blues café in the city,
        opened in 2010, located in the historic monument building, In the 18th century the first (unofficially, of course)
        Iosefine (Radical) masonry was functioning, and then the first literary (German) salon in Cluj. </string>
    <string name="noa_club_description">the place where fashion, luxury and fun meet and merge,
        metamorphosed in a complete, complete, round, unforgettable experience.</string>

    <!-- Addresses -->
    //Must do category
    <string name="cheile_turzii_address">Address: Cheile Turzii, Turda (DN75 Lunca-Turda)</string>
    <string name="cetatuia_address">Address: Strada Călărașilor 1, Cluj-Napoca 34000</string>
    <string name="salina_turda_address">Address: Aleea Durgăului 7, Turda 401106</string>
    <string name="michaels_church_address">Address: Piața Unirii, Cluj-Napoca 400015</string>
    <string name="king_matthias_address">Address: Piața Unirii, Cluj-Napoca</string>

    //Parks category
    <string name="central_park_address">Address: Cluj-Napoca, Strada Cardinal Iuliu Hossu </string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_address">Address: Strada Republicii 42, Cluj-Napoca 400015</string>
    <string name="iulius_park_address">Address: Strada Alexandru Vaida Voevod 53B, Cluj-Napoca 400436</string>
    <string name="rozelor_park_address">Address: Strada Taberei, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="gheorgheni_park_address">Address: Strada Alexandru Vaida Voevod, Cluj-Napoca</string>

    //Shopping category
    <string name="iulius_mall_address">Address: Strada Alexandru Vaida Voevod 53B, Cluj-Napoca 400436</string>
    <string name="vivo_mall_address">Address: Strada Avram Iancu 492"-"500, Florești 407280</string>
    <string name="platinia_mall_address">Address: Calea Manastur 2"-"6</string>

    //History category
    <string name="theotokos_cathedral_address">Address: Piața Avram Iancu, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="franciscan_church_address">Address: Strada Émile Zola 2, Cluj-Napoca 400000</string>
    <string name="ethnografic_museum_address">Address: Memorandumului Street 21, Cluj-Napoca 400114</string>
    <string name="pharmacy_museum_address">Address: Piața Unirii 28</string>
    <string name="observatory_address">Address: Strada Cireșilor 19, Cluj-Napoca 400487</string>
    <string name="art_museum_address">Address: Piața Unirii 30, Cluj-Napoca</string>

    //Nightlife category
    <string name="londoner_pub_address">Address: Strada Émile Zola 5, Cluj-Napoca 400112</string>
    <string name="flying_circus_pub_address">Address: Strada Universității 3, Cluj-Napoca 400000</string>
    <string name="shto_bar_address">Address: Strada Memorandumului 6, Cluj-Napoca 400500</string>
    <string name="bruno_wine_bar_address">Address: Strada Constantin Daicoviciu, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="jazz_pub_address">Address: Strada Vasile Goldiș 2, Cluj-Napoca 400112</string>
    <string name="noa_club_address">Address: Strada Republicii 109, Cluj-Napoca 400000</string>

    <!-- Names of Places -->
    //Must do category
    <string name="cheile_turzii_name">Turda Keys</string>
    <string name="cetatuia_name">Cetatuia</string>
    <string name="salina_turda_name">Salina Turda</string>
    <string name="michaels_church_name">St. Michael\'s Church</string>
    <string name="king_matthias_name">King Matthias Corvin</string>

    //Parks category
    <string name="central_park_name">Central Park</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_name">Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="iulius_park_name">Iulius Park</string>
    <string name="rozelor_park_name">Rozelor Skatepark</string>
    <string name="gheorgheni_park_name">Gheorgheni Complex</string>

    //Shopping category
    <string name="iulius_mall_name">Iulius Mall</string>
    <string name="vivo_mall_name">Vivo! Mall</string>
    <string name="platinia_mall_name">Platinia Shopping Center</string>

    //History category
    <string name="theotokos_cathedral_name">Theotokos Cathedral</string>
    <string name="franciscan_church_name">Franciscan Church</string>
    <string name="ethnografic_museum_name">Museum of Etnografico</string>
    <string name="pharmacy_museum_name">Pharmacy Museum</string>
    <string name="observatory_name">Observatory</string>
    <string name="art_museum_name">Museum of Art</string>

    //Nightlife category
    <string name="londoner_pub_name">The Londoner</string>
    <string name="flying_circus_pub_name">Flying Circus PUB</string>
    <string name="shto_bar_name">Shto College Bar</string>
    <string name="bruno_wine_bar_name">Bruno Wine Bar</string>
    <string name="jazz_pub_name">Casa Jazz</string>
    <string name="noa_club_name">Club NOA</string>

</resources>